JACKIE MORALES

19 Fairfield Avenue, Newington, CT 06111 Home: (860) 665-7722 Cell: (860) 559-3601 E-Mail: jnina721@yahoo.com

SUMMARY

A dedicated bi-lingual administrative professional with 28 years of experience. Extensive knowledge in managing confidential information. Day-to-day experience with working across all levels of leadership and management. Strengths include strong technical support experience and ability to work as an individual contributor or member of a project team.

EXPERIENCE

Aetna, Inc., Hartford, CT

Executive Assistant – Public & Labor	2005 – Present
Executive Assistant – Group Insurance	2003 – 2005
Administrative Assistant – National Accounts & Global Benefits	2001 – 2002
Administrative Executive Assistant – Aetna International	1993 – 2001
Receptionist / Administrative Assistant – Financial Division Systems	1983 – 1993

- Manage calendars and coordinate meetings on executive calendars
- Screen telephone calls, answers questions and provides information as appropriate
- Responsible for all meeting logistics
- Ordering and maintaining marketing promotional items
- Coordinate external professional obligations of managers
- Process all invoices for payments, for medical licenses and memberships
- Provide Spanish to English translation for letters sent to executives
- Produce Strategic and Board of Director Presentations
- Coordinate domestic land & air travel, including submission of all associated travel expenses
- Process all documentation for visa and passport applications
- Produced an International watch list of Country/Competitor Analysis for distribution to the international direct reports
- Responsible for renewal state insurance licenses

ING, Hartford, CT

Administrative Assistant 2002 –2003

- Assisted the management team in organizing several key events: ING Financial Advisers Planning, All Employee meeting, Employee Recognition, and Advisory Summit
- Provided operational support to Career Channel Management team for Career Agent Consultant functions including Tuition Reimbursement processing, general administrative support and monitoring of Agents Benefits programs
- Provided assistance to the Head of Worksite Financial Operations in relation to the new budget systems and the administration of the Fleet Program Administrator (vehicle) program
- Managed budget analysis (creation and development of 2003 Budget) for Broker Dealer Operations and Career Agent Channel Management organization
- Responsible for meeting tight deadlines on invoice and billing processing (Worksite Licenses)

EDUCATION

University of Phoenix-Online, Phoenix, AZ
Hartford Public High School, Hartford, CT
Various Courses
Diploma

ADDITIONAL COURSES, SEMINARS, PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

- Online AXIA University of Phoenix, Phoenix, AZ
- Greater Hartford Community College, Hartford, CT
- Cobol I, Accounting I & II, Micro-Computer in Business
- Catapult Software Training, POWER POINT
- WORD 97 Intermediate & Advance
- Dun & Bradstreet Business Education Services
- American Management Association, Advanced Course in Management Skills for Executive Secretaries and Administrative Assistants
- Alternative Management Systems, Inc. Property Management System
- ICSC Seminar for Shopping Centers
- American Management Association, Advanced Lotus 1-2-3